hyundaicanada.com 2019-05-17

# Privacy Policy | Hyundai Canada

Hyundai Auto Canada Corp. ("Hyundai") respects your privacy and will strive to protect the confidentiality of your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains our policies and practices including why we collect your personal information, how we use it and how we safeguard it. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and if you do not agree with it, please do not provide us with any personal information. 

### Why does Hyundai Collect Personal Information?

We collect your personal information in order to: (a) maintain our records to provide you with warranty or other customer service communications; (b) advise you of any product recalls or customer notifications with respect to your vehicle; (c) provide you with marketing, product information and service offers that may be of interest to you, including targeted content online; (d) provide you with services you request and to respond to your comments or requests for information; (e) conduct market and product preference research and analysis; and, (f) meet our legal obligations and other legitimate business interests. 

### What Personal Information Does Hyundai Collect and How Does Hyundai Collect It?

Hyundai collects personal information about you that is reasonably necessary for the purposes described above. We collect information that will enable us to identify you such as your name, address, e-mail address and telephone number. We may also collect certain demographical information such as family status and purchase preferences. 

We may collect this information directly from you or from our service providers and dealers. When required by law, your personal information is only collected with your consent. For example, we collect financial and credit information about you shared with us by our third party financial service providers when you have provided your consent. When you purchase or lease a vehicle, a Hyundai dealer will collect information about you that will be shared with Hyundai for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. The collection of information shall be subject to any additional terms provided at the time of such transaction. 

Hyundai may also use technology together with your profile information, such as your purchase history, preferences and/or contact information, to provide you with targeted, interest-based and/or behavioral content and advertising and may conduct such activities, as well as data analytics in this respect, in conjunction with third party service providers, social media platforms or other entities. Hyundai and/or other entities, such as ad network providers, publishers and other media entities, may use cookies or other tracking methods to gather information, or otherwise have access to information about you, and may target content to you based on this information and your profile information on various platforms and media. You may choose to alter the settings of your browser to turn off cookies. To opt-out of online advertising programs that track your activities online, visit Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada, NAI opt-out page, the AD Choices Opt-out page and/or any other similarly applicable organization. Opting out in this manner will not prevent advertising from appearing online, but such advertising will not be targeted based on your activities and interests. 

Hyundai conducts contests and offers promotions from time to time and offers services such as vehicle warranty, servicing and maintenance. You may be required to provide certain contact and other information such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, age, and other information that may be required to provide or administer these services or promotions. 

If you do not want us to use this information to contact you for sales or marketing purposes, please call us toll free at 1-888-216-2626 (English or French) Monday to Friday, from 8:30 a.m. to 5:00 p.m. EST. 

### Electronic Data Recorders

Your vehicle may contain an event data recorder (EDR), which can collect and store information about your vehicle and its occupants immediately before and during a collision or near collision event. This information may include information on how various systems in the vehicle were operating, including parameters such as how far the driver was depressing the accelerator or brake pedal, vehicle speed, steering, the use of the front seat belts, as well as diagnostic information and information about the deployment of the airbags and seat belt pretensioners. 

### Visiting the Hyundai Website

You are free to visit the Hyundai website to see and read information about our company and products without providing us with any personal information. We may collect non-personally identifiable information relating to your use of the Hyundai website and e-mails sent by Hyundai, such as which pages you access, which links you clicked, the date and time of your access, information about the internet browser used, your internet service provider and the website from which you accessed our website. If collected, this information will be used to assist us to perform analyses of activity on our website, which we use to help us improve the website. 

In order to provide you with services offered through our website and requested by you (e.g., setting up a test drive or receiving updates from us) we may require that you provide certain personal information. By providing us with such information you are consenting to the collection, use and disclosure by us, our dealers and our service providers of the information as required to provide the requested service. Unless you request us not to do so, you also agree that personal information provided by you may be used by us and disclosed to our dealers and service providers for the purpose of including you in advertising and marketing programs designed to increase awareness of Hyundai products and services which we, our dealers and/or service providers believe will be of interest to you. For example, we may send you such things as information concerning promotional offers. 

Our website may contain links to other websites. We urge you to review the privacy statements of each website that you visit to ensure that you understand when, how and why those websites use and share your personal information. Hyundai makes no representation or warranty as to the accuracy, completeness, or authenticity of any information contained in any such linked website, including the website’s privacy statements or data handling practices. Any link to any other person or entity’s website should not in any manner be construed as endorsement by Hyundai of such person or entity's website, products or services. 

Your use of our website constitutes acceptance of this Privacy Policy and any modifications thereto in effect. If the terms of this Privacy Policy are at any time unacceptable to you, do not provide us with any personal information through our website. 

### How Does Hyundai Share Personal Information?

Hyundai may share your personal information with our dealers, affiliates and service providers. Hyundai may also share your personal information with our service providers for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. Before we share your information with any third party, we will obtain your consent as required by applicable law. For example, we may share your personal information with our service providers exclusively for the purpose of providing services for us (e.g., to fulfill your request to enter into a Hyundai contest). We require that our service providers that have access to your personal information keep the information confidential and they are not permitted to use your personal information for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are providing to us. 

We may also disclose your information as required by law. 

### Information May Be Located Outside of Canada

Third party service providers to whom we disclose personal information pursuant to this policy may be located outside of Canada. If our service provider is located in a foreign jurisdiction they are bound by the laws of the country in which they are located. As a result, they may be required to disclose your personal information in response to demands from government authorities, law enforcement, or courts of their jurisdictions. 

### Retention of Personal Information

The length of time we keep your personal information varies depending on the services being provided to you. We have retention standards that meet customer service, legal and regulatory needs as well as our internal record retention practices. 

### Accuracy and Updating Personal Information

We take care to ensure that the information we have is accurate and up-to-date. However, we also rely on you to tell us when your personal information changes. You can access, update and correct errors in your personally identifiable information by contacting us at 1.888.216.2626 or by clicking on “Update My Communication Preferences” on the bottom of this page. Depending on the nature of the information you are requesting and the complexity of your request, we may ask you to put your request in writing. 

### Hyundai Safeguards Your Personal Information

Hyundai is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information in compliance with this Privacy Policy and applicable laws. We limit access to your personal information and ensure that it is securely stored. Access to your personal information is given only to those who require it for the purposes identified in this Privacy Policy. 

We are committed to upholding our Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or about how we are complying with the Privacy Policy, let us know. In most cases, a question or concern is resolved simply by talking to us about it. You can contact our Privacy Officer at: 

Hyundai Auto Canada Corp.

75 Frontenac Drive

Markham, Ontario L3R 6h5

Attention: Privacy Officer

If the above steps fail to resolve your question or concern, you may also contact the Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada: 

Place de Ville

112 Kent Street, 3rd Floor

Ottawa, Ontario

K1A 1H3

Call toll free at 1.800.282.1376

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time and at our sole discretion, without notice. Changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective immediately on posting to our website. You agree to review this Privacy Policy on each visit to our website to inform yourself of any such modifications. You also agree to be bound by any such modifications.
